PILOT [OVER PA]:
Ladies and gentlemen...
...we are beginning our descent
into Berlin Tegel...
...where local time is 8:30 a.m. and the
temperature is a cool minus four degrees.
Morning.
Did you sleep?
No. I'll sleep at the hotel.
You'll do great.
You always do.
What's the purpose of your visit?
We're here for a biotechnology summit.
I'm giving a presentation.
Mr. and Mrs. Harris, welcome to Berlin.
MARTIN:
Danke schön.
IMMIGRATION OFFICER:
Next, please.
"I'm giving a presentation"?
Well, she asked.
-Oof. Welcome to Berlin.
MAN: Taxi.
Taxi.
Martin, get in the car. Let him do that.
Oh, ya-ya.
What do you think he's saying?
No idea.
Look. Isabel Kronenberger is showing
here on Saturday.
Oh, yeah.
Remember when we saw her
in Chicago?
Yes.
Why don't I meet you there on Saturday
after my lunch with Professor Bressler?
Yeah.
If you promise.
I promise.
-Welcome to the Hotel Adlon Kempinski.
MARTIN: Thank you.
You check in, honey.
I'll take care of this.
Have you stayed with us before?
-First time in Berlin.
RECEPTIONIST:
If there's anything eIse l can do for you....
How much do I owe you?
DRIVER:
Thirty-seven, sir.
Welcome to the Adlon Kempinski Berlin.
How may l help you, madam?
-Dr. and Mrs. Harris, the Eisenhower suite.
-Of course.
MARTIN: Wait, wait.
-Everything okay, sir?
-Is this everything from the taxi?
-Yes, sir.
I'm afraid, Mrs. Harris, but the Eisenhower
suite may not be available right now.
What do you mean "not available"?
There have been changes,
security reasons.
But we confirmed two weeks ago.
Would you allow me
to answer the phone?
MARTIN:
I'll go to the airport. l'll be back, okay?
Oh, please.
Excuse me, driver?
Is there another route?
Oh, come on.
-Look out!
-No!
Hello? Hello?
Can you hear me?
Dr. Farge?
Dr. Farge. Dr. Farge.
I don't speak German.
FARGE:
Are you English?
American.
You have been in an accident.
Accident?
Can you tell me your name?
Your name.
Martin. Martin Harris.
Dr. Martin Harris.
Where's my wife, Liz?
-Is she hurt? Is she hurt? Where is she?
-Calm down.
It's all right, Dr. Harris.
You were the only passenger.
The taxi you were in went into the river.
Your heart stopped for several minutes.
It's Thursday, November 24th.
You have been in a coma for four days.
Thanksgiving.
But my wife, she's in Berlin with me.
Where is she? Why isn't she here?
We couldn't find any identification
with you, Dr. Harris.
No, no, no.
-Please, calm down.
MARTIN: Aah.
Where can we reach your wife?
Does she have a cell phone?
Of course she has a cell phone. It's....
Uh....
I can't remember.
Can you tell me what you do remember,
Martin?
Bits and pieces. Arriving at the airport.
Getting in a taxi with Liz...
...but l don't know how l got here.
There are no rules with severe trauma
of this kind.
Memories get lost or fractured.
Most of them return,
aIthough it's unlikely...
...you will ever fully recall the events
around your accident.
In the meantime, let us see
if anyone has filed a report...
...looking for a Martin Harris, okay?
-Yes, yes, yes.
-Okay.
ANNOUNCER: From London
with Kevin Spencer and Diana Bailey.
Good evening.
Welcome to the BNI World News.
Here are today's top stories.
The Prime Mini--
Clothes. For you.
MARTIN: Has anybody been
looking for me? My wife?
Meine Frau?
Come here, you.
It's beautiful. Just beautiful.
LIZ:
I'm glad you like it.
She gave it to me as a gift.
In Paris. On our honeymoon.
Prince Shada arrived in Berlin today for
this year's biotechnology global summit.
The personal attendance
of the flamboyant prince...
...has fueled speculation that the summit,
now in its 10th year...
...will witness the announcement
of a major scientific breakthrough.
With the world's leading researchers
convening...
...at the luxurious Hotel Adlon
in Central Berlin...
-Hotel Adlon.
-...the field of biotechnology...
...steps into the forefront
of the media spotlight.
I'm here for the summit.
Nurse.
You have to realize the risk.
Doctor, I've been gone for four days.
My wife is out there in a city
she doesn't know. She'll be terrified.
I need to find her.
Sign this.
It releases you from my care.
And here's my card.
Any nausea, dizziness, difficuIty with
speech, you contact me immediately.
-Do you understand?
-Thank you.
Welcome to the Hotel Adlon Kempinski.
How may l help you?
Yes, hi. I'm a guest of the hotel.
I lost my room key. I need a new one.
-What room are you staying in?
-The Eisenhower suite.
-And may l have your name?
-Martin Harris. Dr. Martin Harris.
And may l please see some lD,
Mr. Harris?
There's been a situation.
I've lost my passport.
I'm going to need some lD, sir.
If you get someone to escort me
to my room, I can prove it.
Just give me a moment.
-Excuse me. Do you have an invitation?
-No.
I mean, yes. My name is Dr. Martin Harris.
I'm on the list.
-Let me check.
-l saw my wife go inside.
I'm trying to find her.
Herr Strauss?
-Dr. Martin Harris?
-Yes.
Yes. There you are. I'm Herr Strauss,
head of the Hotel Security.
Do you have any identification?
Passport, driver's license?
No, I don't, but--
-You would know him, he's over there.
-Professor Bressler!
STRAUSS: Sir, please.
He knows me.
He can confirm who I am.
-If you will be patient, sir, no problem.
-I'm being very patient.
Thank God. There she is. That's my wife,
over there by the buffet table.
I have been missing for four days and she
has no idea what happened to me...
...so l need you to take me to her
right now.
-Okay.
-Thank you.
-The lady in the dark dress.
-Okay.
Excuse me, madam.
Your husband is here.
Liz. Oh, Jesus.
Excuse me. Do I know you?
But, Liz-- What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
I was in an accident. I was in a coma.
They didn't know who l was.
I said I'm sorry.
Oh, you must have me confused
with someone eIse.
MARTIN:
Liz.
It's me, Martin.
Your husband.
This is a misunderstanding.
I don't know this man.
-Okay.
-Martin.
This is my husband.
You are Dr. Martin Harris?
Last time l looked.
Yep, still me.
What's going on here?
Is this some kind of a joke?
Joke about what?
Because it's not very funny.
-Do you know this man?
-No.
Who the hell are you?
I'm her husband.
Okay. Okay.
Would you mind just getting him
away from us, please?
-Liz. Liz, stop this.
MARTIN B: Hey.
-Gentlemen, please, please, please.
-Get your hands off me.
MARTIN B: Back off.
-What's going on?
-Tell me.
-Back off!
-What's this all about?
MARTIN B: Why don't you take a walk?
STRAUSS:
Gentlemen, please.
-Don't touch me.
-Come on, come on!
If you don't leave now,
we have to call the police.
Call the police! Call the goddamn army!
That's a good idea!
What's happening?
You're embarrassing me. Please.
-Get him out of here.
-Liz!
-l must apologize. Have a nice evening.
-l was hurt!
-Liz! Why are you doing this to me?
MARTIN B: You okay?
Can you believe this?
Right there.
That's Liz. And l am....
I must've been outside.
I can't remember.
Well, as you can see, you are not there.
OFFICER: lmmigration confirms the arrival
of a Dr. and Mrs. Harris...
-...on November the 20th at 7:40 a.m.
-Yes.
At 8:50, she checked into their suite
at the hotel...
...followed by Dr. Harris
at 3 in the afternoon.
-What?
-Danke.
Wait. He's-- He's not Martin Harris.
I am Dr. Martin Harris.
The man upstairs is pretending
to be me.
And this impostor,
did he aIso steal your wife?
He must be forcing her or something.
Well, why? Help me. Why?
For God's sake,
just do an lnternet search.
There are over 400 Martin Harrises
in the United States, sir.
We already checked.
Rod. Rodney Cole,
a colleague at Langemore in the States.
A dear friend.
He can verify who l am.
Please, call him. It's 001 ...
...508-146-2595.
RODNEY [ON RECORDING]:
This is Dr. Cole. I'm having an....
Sorry, answering machine.
Please, leave a message.
Professor Bressler. Talk to him.
He's the reason I'm in Berlin.
He invited me over to the summit
to discuss my thesis.
-You know Professor Bressler?
-Yes.
Well, we haven't actually met,
but we've been speaking on the phone...
...e-mailing, dozens of times.
-Why don't you arrest him?
STRAUSS: For what?
Entering the country legally?
Presenting all the correct documentation
and sharing a hotel suite with his wife?
Excuse me. With your wife.
She is my wife.
Herr Strauss? l found a Dr. Martin Harris
at Langemore University.
Yes. Thank you.
That's what I've been trying....
Okay.
Wait, please, wait.
You're going to arrest me?
I demand to speak to my embassy.
Unfortunately, it's your Thanksgiving.
The embassy's closed until Monday.
Herr Strauss,
can l have a quiet word, please?
Okay.
Listen...
...you're probably right. I--
The accident.
I, uh--
I haven't been remembering things
very well. I'm confused.
This is my doctor
at the hospital here in Berlin.
He warned me that this sort of thing,
this was gonna happen.
I need to go back there now.
I'm so embarrassed.
So now you are saying
that you are not Dr. Martin Harris?
I don't know.
Wait, stop. Stop. I've changed my mind.
-Need passport.
-Please.
Please?
Police. Very bad.
RODNEY [ON RECORDING]:
This is Dr. Cole.
I'm having an out-of-office experience
right now. Please1 leave a message.
Rodney, it's me, Martin.
Listen, I'm in Berlin
for the summit, but....
It's Liz. She's--
I-- l don't know what she's doing...
...and there's another man involved.
It-- She-- She....
I'm in trouble, Rod. We--
Shit.
MAN: He says he doesn't caye
if she saved your life.
The bitch cost him 20,000 Euros.
The insurance won't cover the cab
as she had no license.
He says illegal immigrants
are destroying German society.
So I'm guessing he doesn't know
where she is.
No one knows where she is.
Well, thank him for his time.
MARTIN:
Excuse me.
Hey, American.
I'm sorry we couldn't help you.
You know where she is, l can tell.
Look, l just wanna thank her.
She saved my life.
I thought maybe l could give her
some money. I just wanna thank her.
Please.
You remember me?
-l was in your taxi.
-l don't drive taxi.
MARTIN:
I was in your taxi.
We crashed.
I need to know,
where did you pick me up?
-Where was I going?
-How did you find me?
Your friend, Biko.
Just leave me alone.
MARTIN:
Please, help me.
Just leave me alone.
Thank you for saving me.
Excuse me.
I need to find Professor Bressler's lab.
I have an appointment at 1 2:30. I'm late.
-Your name, please?
-Dr. Martin Harris.
Wait here, please.
The professor knows who l am.
We scheduled this appointment
weeks ago.
MARTIN B:
Drake, the English botanist...
...who wondered how it manages
to reproduce...
...as it doesn't appear to attract
any insects.
Yes. One wonders how plants are
developing firm, unlike m--
-Bressler.
-This lab is restricted. Who are you?
This man is not Martin Harris.
I am Dr. Martin Harris.
So, what is this?
There are two Martin Harrises, huh?
MARTIN B:
No, let me explain.
This man showed up at my hotel last night
claiming to be me.
-The police were called.
-l called the police, son of a bitch!
He checked himself out of a hospital.
-He was in an accident.
-Professor.
Ja. Danke.
We talked, you and I, on the phone.
We discussed
aIternative forms of propagation.
I told you about my father,
a schooIteacher, his passion for science.
We talked about your children...
...about how much time you've spent
with them since you lost your wife.
Two girls, right?
You told me their names. And I....
I just can't....
I know them. l know them.
-Laurel.
MARTIN B: Laurel, Lily, twins.
Ten years old.
About the same age I was when l told
my father I wanted to be a botanist.
Do you remember, Professor?
We talked about that on the phone...
...how l'd never seen my father
this happy.
No, that wasn't you.
Don't you remember? We spoke
about how brave our wives were--
BOTH:
To marry scientists.
-l told you about our--
-Our honeymoon in Paris.
My wife and l. And how she wanted to visit
all the museums.
-All l wanted to do was go to the--
BOTH: L'Ecole Polytechnique.
BOTH: But she insisted. And that's how
I first saw Leonardo's Vitruvian man.
Wow.
This is not happening.
STUDENT:
Moment, Moment.
I don't know who this man is,
but he has taken everything from me.
You have to arrest him.
Go on, arrest him.
I don't believe l need to do this.
MARTIN:
No.
My friend, he...
...looks....
No, he finds people.
FARGE:
Martin.
The mistake was mine.
I should never have let you leave.
-What's happening to me, doctor?
-Confusion...
...memory loss,
complete or partial loss of identity.
These are common stages in recovery.
A person can awaken from a coma...
...convinced of a reality
that was previously only fantasy.
We are going to sedate you now...
...do another MRI,
try to find out what's going on, okay?
If I'm not Martin Harris,
why do l know so much about him?
Perhaps he was someone
you read about...
...or met once in passing.
Do you know what it feels like
to become insane, doctor?
It's like a war
between being told who you are...
...and knowing who you are.
Which do you think wins?
Hello, Martin. This won't take very long.
GRETCHEN:
SMITH:
It's okay. I'm feeling much, much better.
MAN [ON TV]: And now with us,
Rebecca for the weather.
Hello?
REBECCA [ON TV]: So it's going to be
a cold night here in Central Berlin...
...with an overnight low
of three degrees...
...and a high probability of more snow
throughout tomorrow.
And now to the West1
to the Ruhy Valley.
-Herr Jörgen?
-Yeah?
You met her?
She looked after me in the hospital.
She was kind to me too.
I'm sorry. She's dead.
Come. Come in.
Thank you.
Drink?
No, thanks.
I was a former member of the Stasi...
...the Ministry for State Security.
-East German secret police, huh?
-Yes.
Proudly.
Excuse me.
I cannot drink any longer,
but I like to forget that.
We Germans are experts at forgetting.
We forgot we were Nazis.
Now we have forgotten 40 years
of Communism, all gone.
But it's not just history that's forgotten,
it's people too.
Please tell me more about
Nurse Gretchen Herfort.
Quite a story.
For a moment,
they had me convinced l was crazy.
But when they came to take me,
when they...
...killed your friend, l knew.
I'm not sure how l can be of service.
I need you to help me prove I'm me.
May I?
Please.
It's a gift from my father.
I always have it with me.
These mean anything to you?
No. It's my wife's writing.
So they mean something to her.
That's my schedule for this week.
I wrote it from memory.
Your wife's involvement in this.
There must have been something in
the past, a new friend, an acquaintance?
No, no, no.
Unexplained absence?
No, no. There was nothing.
I would've known.
Men always like to think.
It's not Liz. l know her.
Yet she does not know you.
Look, whoever's been doing this,
they've been planning it for some time.
They have passports, credit cards,
family photos, for God's sakes.
I mean, this takes preparation,
doesn't it?
They have detailed knowledge of my
research, my relationship with Professor--
As well as the fact that you were going
to have a random accident...
...that would allow a stranger
to seamlessly take your place?
These people may be good,
but they are not God.
A little confirmation would be nice.
Somewhere there's proof.
They can't have thought of everything.
The question is,
why would they want to take your place?
What could they gain from being you?
What does your wife gain
by denying you exist?
Do you believe me?
In the Stasi, we had a basic principle:
Ask enough questions and a man who
is lying will eventually change his story...
...but a man who telIs the truth
cannot change his...
...however unlikely his story sounds.
-Do you believe me?
-l believe...
...you are telling the truth, Dr. Harris.
I'll start by calling your colleague
at Langemore.
As you say, it's Thanksgiving,
and there's the time difference...
...so it may take time to make contact.
Then there is the question of....
Oh, of money. Of course.
Unfortunately, yes. Money.
Of course. Here.
Here's everything l have.
I'll pay you in full as soon as l can.
-For expenses.
-Sure.
I'll need 24 hours.
Call me tomorrow afternoon.
And go find your taxi driver.
See if she'll talk to me.
She was there at the beginning of all this.
Perhaps she knows something.
I've already tried.
There may be detaiIs we've overlooked.
That's what l was really known for,
detaiIs.
MARTIN:
Gina?
I know why you ran away
from the accident.
You're an illegal.
If the police had picked you up,
they would have deported you.
Look, l want you to have this.
-What if l don't want it?
-It's worth at least 5000 Euro.
Feel the weight of it.
Go on. It's the real thing.
"E.H. to M.H."?
Elizabeth Harris, my wife, to me, Martin.
Special gift.
Okay, Martin Harris.
What do you want?
There's someone
I need you to speak to.
-I'm not talking to the police.
-He's not the police. I promise you.
I just need you to tell him
what happened.
Anything,
everything you can remember.
And l need a place to crash tonight.
Please?
Sentiment,
it's always the first thing to go.
OFFICER [IN GERMAN]:
Brandt.
Jörgen?
I picked you up from the Adlon Hotel.
You wanted to go to the airport.
You were in a hurry.
That's it?
But l'd just arrived.
Doesn't make sense.
She didn't recognize you?
How long have you been married?
-Five years.
-Five years?
I know it sounds crazy, but it's true.
This is it.
Sorry, no elevator.
I know, not the Adlon Hotel.
The walIs are made of cardboard,
but it's home.
I have to work tonight.
You can sleep in there.
I have extra mattress.
MARTIN:
It's quaint.
Would you mind if l took a shower?
You could try. I'm not sure you will fit.
The light is broken. You need to leave
the door open if you want to see anything.
-I'm sorry. I just-- I'm sorry.
-l give you a place to stay.
-That does not give you the right to--
-You're right.
They're good, the drawings.
You want to know?
This is me.
Two thousand
two hundred fifty-eight Euros...
...and counting.
I get to 4000, l can buy papers
so l can get the hell out of here.
Sell the watch.
You'll get more than you need.
I plan to.
Ohh.
How do you sleep?
Eh. He never goes for very long.
This guy, Jörgen.
He's absolutely no danger to you.
Okay.
Hello.
You got company.
Do you have the keys?
Bring it back to my place,
leave the keys on the TV...
...and don't forget to reset the meter.
-You're the best.
-l know. Come.
Yes, l sleep with every American
you send my way.
No need to explain.
GINA:
Biko! You're going to be late.
Shh.
Jones?
Biko? Biko?
Who are you?
Who the hell are you?
Biko's keys.
Give them to me.
Come on, you can't stay here.
This one!
Are you all right?
That guy,
he killed a nurse in the hospital.
-What?
-He killed a nurse.
Shit!
-Left, go left!
-Hang on!
-Where is he?
-l can't see him.
-Where is--? Where's the wiper switch?
-It's on the left!
Shit!
Come on! Go!
-Get off the tracks!
-I'm trying to!
Jesus!
Come on, come on! Go!
GINA: - Come on!
MARTIN: - Run!
GINA:
In here.
MARTIN:
Out of the way. Out of the way.
-We are being followed.
-Vladimir.
How does it feel
To treat me like you do?
When you've laid youy hands upon me
And you've told me who you aye
I thought l was mistaken
How do l feel?
Tell me now how do I feel?
Gina.
You have to know l have never laid eyes
on those men.
Why the hell did you
have to get into my taxi?
I wish I hadn't. Believe me.
And Biko. His family is in Africa.
The money will just stop coming.
They will never know why.
Men like that, back there.
I have seen those kind of men before.
They killed my family in Bosnia.
My mother, my father, my brothers,
slaughtered!
We have to disappear.
-Gina, they're after me, not you.
-Don't be stupid. They're after both of us!
If they killed Biko,
they'll kill me just as easily.
Are you ready?
Don't ask.
Thank you.
I'm sorry I brought more trouble
into your life.
I will try and make up for it. I promise.
I know.
I've figured something out.
MARTIN:
It's a simple code.
The first number refers to a page
in the book...
...the second to a line on that page,
the third to words on that line.
What are the words?
The Latin names of two plant species:
Calochortus albus
and Umbellularia Californica.
Fairy Lantern and California Bay,
both common, flowering plants.
What does it mean?
That I don't know.
Not part of your work,
or Professor Bressler's?
No.
Tell me, Martin, how close
are Professor Bressler and Prince Shada?
Very close. The prince is sponsoring
the summit. They're both progressives.
Bressler wants to end world hunger.
He's researching new forms
of crop cuItivation...
...offering open access to his data.
The prince funds his work.
He knows the world will need food
long after his oil resources are depleted.
Those agricuItural patents
will be worth a fortune.
But the prince's progressiveness
has cost him.
Extremists in his own country
hate him...
...and yet he perseveres his course,
despite muItiple attempts on his life.
There's a cocktail party before Bressler's
speech tonight, is that correct?
Yes.
For some, that might be a very good
reason to want to be you.
Martin Harris with just a few guests...
...in a confined space
with Prince Shada.
Jörgen may be right,
but he might not be able to prove it.
I need to find Liz.
Oh, Martin, that is not a good idea.
The people who have her
have been sticking to my schedule.
I know where she'll be today.
Someone will be watching her.
What if he's there?
He won't be. He's me, remember?
He'll be meeting with Bressler.
-Yeah?
-They just sat down.
Let me know when they leave. Thanks.
MARTIN B:
Okay.
WOMAN [ON RECORDING]:
Please leave a message after the tone.
MARTIN:
Liz.
What are you doing here?
Liz. What's happening?
Are you crazy?
You have to leave me alone.
Why? You have to tell me why.
Are they making you do this?
-Are they threatening you?
-How did you find me? Did you follow me?
When we arrived, you saw the ad.
You mentioned when we first saw
her show, in Chicago, together.
Don't you remember?
-l can't get out.
-Come with me right now.
No. They'll kill us both.
I never should have left you.
I never should have gotten into that taxi.
You don't understand, do you?
Your briefcase.
It got left behind at the airport.
That's why you were going back.
You need to find it.
Wait for me there.
Liz, Liz, wait.
I love you.
-What did she say?
-Not here.
MARTIN B:
Where have you been? Hm?
I have to go to the airport right away.
Ja?
RODNEy: Is this Ernst Jörgen?
-Yes, it is.
My name is Rodney Cole.
I received a phone message from you.
And l received two from Martin as well.
What's the problem?
Oh, dear. Oh, that's unbelievable.
The poor man.
Well, listen, here's the good news.
I've just arrived in Berlin.
Yes, I've been teaching in Leipzig,
at the Hochschule für Technik.
I'm sorry, please excuse my German.
Well, l came up for the last day
to hear Bressler's speech.
I could come right over.
No, no, no, it's fine.
It's no problem at all. It's not far.
I know exactly where you aye.
I look forward to meeting you, Mr. Cole.
Well, then1 l'll see you soon. Bye.
Rodney Cole?
Leipzig?
RODNEY:
Herr Jörgen?
Dr. Cole.
How do you do?
Thank you.
Drink?
I have a bottle labeled brandy,
which is more than likely hair lacquer...
...or some vodka my neighbor gave me
after it made her husband go blind.
No, thank you.
Maybe some coffee?
I'm making some for myself.
No, I'm fine. Thank you.
You were in the military.
In the Stasi in East Germany.
Well, my grandson's gonna be
very excited to hear that.
He loves all this Cold War stuff.
Oh, look at that.
What kind of car is that?
That's a Volga GAZ-24.
Suspension of a donkey cart
and smelled like a tannery.
Vanished as quickly as the Wall.
Oh. This business with Martin
is a hell of a thing. How did he find you?
Quite by chance, as it happens.
I would say he was damn lucky.
How can l help?
Come with us to the authorities.
Help them confirm his identity.
The authorities?
Oh, Jesus. Is it that bad?
I mean, a man comes to you with a story.
Why did you take his case?
Eh. Curiosity.
Is that all?
There's not much in this world left
to interest an old spy like me.
A few questions l still think over.
One in particular
from when I worked for the Aufklärung...
...our Foreign Intelligence wing.
They used to talk about
a European-based assassination unit...
...called Section 15.
Freelance, deniable.
They'd work for whoever would pay.
Public sector, private sector.
Second-to-none
in their planning and efficiency.
What's more, they never failed.
And l am told
they are still in existence...
...but that's only rumor, of course.
You had time after l called you.
Why didn't you run?
Where should l run from Section 15,
Mr. Cole?
I can hardly walk.
Before we could get Chesterfields,
I smoked 60 machorkas a day.
FiIthy Soviet things.
Killed more Russians than Stalin.
My doctors assure me
I'll soon be joining their list of casuaIties.
I want to know how he found you.
I want every name,
every source you contacted on his behaIf.
And then what?
We shake hands and you go away?
Cyanide.
You never think you'll have the courage
to use it.
But you do.
The best of us do.
What if he remembers everything?
What then?
Wait, wait. Please.
The combination for the lock is....
Two eight zero...
Two eight zero six three five.
MARTIN:
Who am l?
May I?
You shouldn't stay here.
It's not safe for you.
Liz told me to wait here.
Where are you going?
You've got your life back.
I'm happy for you.
Now I need to get on with mine.
Gina.
Thank you.
It's more than l need.
It's less than you deserve.
For everything you've been through.
Go on, take it.
What if she told them
where you were going?
Liz? She wouldn't.
How do you know?
Gina, she's my wife.
Yes, she is.
It's too heavy for me.
Martin.
Oh, my God, look at you.
How are you doing?
Rodney? What are you doing here?
Well, you called me.
Don't you remember?
You left a message on my machine.
I got on the first plane l could.
-What have you gotten yourself into?
-I'm sorry to drag you into this, but--
Don't be. We've been friends
for 15 years.
I know you'd do the same for me.
Let me take that for you, huh?
I've never had this happen before.
You really think you are Martin Harris,
don't you?
What the hell, Rod?
You're my oldest friend.
You know who l am. It's me.
It's not this other guy. He's not--
Martin Harris? No, course he's not.
But, then, neither are you.
-What?
-There is no Martin Harris.
He doesn't exist.
You invented him.
He's your legend.
You just made him up as a cover
to get into the conference.
-You're not making sense. Liz--
-Liz.
Liz is not your wife.
You were a professional team.
No. No, no. This is insane. She--
Your memories are not real.
Martin Harris is a fabrication.
You just invented a life,
and then you filled in the gaps.
She's right. You're really gone on this.
She had to go in with a backup.
How do you think she feels?
They're gonna write
a textbook on you someday.
And thank you for retrieving the briefcase
from the airport.
Leaving it there was untidy.
It was a loose end
that didn't fit in with our plans...
...and Jörgen figured us out.
By the way, he's dead.
And he died very well.
And I'm afraid that isn't something
I'm gonna be able to say about you.
I'm sorry.
I'm really, really sorry.
Rodney!
MARTIN:
Why are you doing this?
One year of preparation.
We did everything we could
to make you come back.
Do you know how much time
you've wasted? It's Thanksgiving.
I could've been home with my family,
having dinner...
...instead of cleaning up your mess
because you bumped your head...
...and started to believe your cover.
Tell me...
...who am I?
You were a trained assassin,
and you were my best boy.
And now you're just gonna be
another nameless dead junkie.
Gina, stay down!
Gina. Gina.
No. No.
"Martin Harris...
...married to Elizabeth Terman,
July 1 8, 2006, Martha's Vineyard.
Father died, September 9, 1 987,
of a heart attack."
I made it up. I made it up
to kill a man I've never met.
Look, August 27th, the entry stamp.
You were in Berlin three months ago.
-Are you ready?
MARTIN: Almost.
Ready.
Who are these people?
They can become anyone.
They....
We are killers.
Prince Shada
is gonna be assassinated tonight.
There's a bomb in his suite.
I put it there.
You should've let me drown.
What matters is what you do now,
Martin.
REPORTER 2: Prince Shada,
are you going to stay in Berlin?
REPORTER 3: Will you be funding
research at the university?
REPORTER 4: Are you interested
in GM crops, Prince Shada?
REPORTER 5: How long have you been
working with Professor Bressler?
GUARD:
We're so honored you could attend.
The honor is all mine.
Would you like a drink?
In some circles...
...my husband is more well-known
for his martinis than his research.
GUARD: Do you have an invitation, sir?
-l don't know if I'm supposed to have...
-...an invitation.
-Leo, please, come in.
I don't think you need
an invitation to your reception.
BRESSLER:
Good to see you.
So good to see you.
Have you met our host?
-Not yet.
-Hello.
Now I can see why
somebody would pretend to be him.
MARTIN:
This way.
Oh, let me take that.
-l'd rather hold on to this, if you don't mind.
-Oh, you can trust me, Professor.
Separation anxiety.
-Just leave it there, if you could.
-Of course.
Thank you.
Danke.
SHADA:
Come, say hello to my friends.
Danke schön.
Oh, excuse me.
MARTIN B:
It's you.
SHADA:
I am not so sure about that.
Many of my relatives would not agree.
This way.
Get your hands off her!
Okay, I'm coming.
There's a bomb in the Eisenhower suite.
I put it there three months ago!
Now you are saying you are
Dr. Martin Harris?
MARTIN:
You're not listening!
Take me to the room.
I'll show you exactly where it is.
Up to the room, in the middle of a party
with Prince Shada...
...and the world's leading scientific minds?
Of course, why didn't you say so before?
I'm not lying! Pull up the reception
recordings from August 27th of this year.
Do it now, or many people will die!
-Excuse me, I'm going to grab my bag.
-Sure.
Here. Why don't you just wear it?
Like some nerdy accessory?
BRESSLER:
Oh.
Thank you.
-That's got all your secrets in it, right?
BRESSLER: If you'd like to say so....
Would you excuse me?
I have to go check on something.
Stop. Stop. That's it.
Do you see? Look! Do you see?
WOMAN [OVER PA]:
Attention1 attention...
...could all guests leave the hotel
by the front entrance?
MARTIN B: - Shit.
WOMAN: - Attention, attention...
...could all guests leave the hotel
by the front entrance?
Find the target. Finish it.
We got what we came for.
I'm going to take care of the bomb.
-Forget about it.
-They have my image on file...
-...from when we planted it.
-So?
I don't want my face connected
to an explosion we no longer need.
Go!
Lily, Laurel.
Bressler's girls. Lily, Laurel.
Flowering plants.
Calochortus albus
and Umbellularia Californica.
The code, from the book.
They're his passwords.
Bressler's supposedly working
on a new strain of corn.
One that can grow in any climate.
It's revolutionary.
If they access his research
and kill him...
...it could be worth billions
in the wrong hands.
Laurel! Laurel!
-Papa!
-Laurel!
That bomb goes off, it'll look as if
Shada was killed by extremists.
The prince was never the target.
It's Bressler.
Listen, listen! You have to tell Strauss,
they're after Bressler!
Do you understand?
Go! Go!
Out of the way! Move! Move!
-Laurel! Laurel!
LAUREL: Papa!
Laurel! Laurel!
Oh, Laurel.
Papa!
She was wandering around,
looking for you.
-Thank you.
-You're welcome.
-We have to leave.
-Yes, yes.
Christ, you really don't
remember anything, do you?
MARTIN:
This'll be at the party...
...where we'll access Bressler's computer
and steal his files.
The client wants this clean.
He wants the material from Bressler's
computer and Bressler dead.
No one can ever know what happened.
MARTIN: When the bomb goes off,
it'll appear that Shada was the target...
...and that Bressler
was collateral damage.
Looks great.
MARTIN B:
Time for the A team?
I didn't forget everything.
I remember how to kill you, asshole.
REPORTER [ON TV]: Less than 24 hours
after the failed assassination attempt...
...on the Saudi prince...
...Nobel laureate Professor Leo Bressler
announced the development...
...of a new strain of corn...
...fast-growing, self-propagating,
drought-tolerant, and pest-resistant...
...to be made available worldwide
without patent oy copyright costs.
We have made the genetic map
of this new sustenance available to all.
It's a gift. It's a gift from Prince Shada
and from science to mankind.
REPORTER: Humanitarian organizations
applauded the announcement...
...but agri-business companies
weye taken by suyprise...
...and watched as stocks plunged
14 percent.
This is Annabelle Mandeng reporting
from Berlin.
BAILEY: And in other news1 the European
Payliament today passed legislation...
...to remove trade tariffs
on imported African rice...
...with 582 members of the 736-seat body
voting to ratify the measure.
Hey. Now you're free
to do whatever you want.
GINA:
Claudia Marie Taylor.
-I like it.
-lt suits you.
Who are you?
Henry. Henry Taylor.
Ahh. Nice to meet you, Mr. Taylor.
Nice to meet you.